Hello everyone, welcome back to today's another new tutorial topic. So today here, I'll create the
SQL for the limit in the posterior SQL, which allows us to limit the number of rows written by the
SQL statement. Okay, so here the limit plus post-grid SQL is the handy tool for controlling the
size of the result, set written by query and specific useful when dealing with the last data set
of point, you only need to view the subset of the data. Okay, so first of all here, I can simply just
use for the new table and the limit and then offset allows us to retrieve for the proportion
of the row and generated by the rest of the queries. Okay, so here I can simply use for the new table
and have any requests. So again, first of all, here and select for the table. So now just I can
use for the select first and use for the multiplication sign and use for the company data table. Okay,
so now here select and then execute and you can see this company table,
break. Okay, so here, this table, the limit and also for the offset. Okay, so first of all,
here I can use for the example and this limit, the row of the table is according to the number
of rows beyond to fetch from the table. Okay, so first of all, here we can use for the three tables.
Okay, the number I can type for the select multiplication from and we can use for the limit for
limit is two. Okay, so here I can simply just use and then type for the execute and select and
you can see here simply in the session for limit is not defined here. So now the start three and
because in the statement is correctly but not apply this incorrect here, the same topic. So
now we can use for the another example to use here. So the next session,
you can need to pick up the set of record for a particular offset and suppose here,
the example, please pick up three records starting from the third position. Okay,
so here I can use for the limit is one. Okay, and now here I can use for
simply just use the limit and now here I can use for the offset. Okay, so this is the offset for
two. Okay, so you can see here same for the row because I'm not
assigning this progress. So now just try just using execute and you can see the same problem
here. So now we can try perfectly and see the result for in the display and here is first to
statements is perfectly correct. Okay, so here you can choose for another way to define for this
example. Okay, so here I can create for another example just define for the statement for the syntax.
So now here, I can use for the phase for the first syntax to reach out the first three
and first two rows from the employee table after sorting its salary in the listening order. Okay,
so just have the define for the data syntax and just try for the
create completely and see the results for in your desktop or the laptop computer. Okay,
so first of all here I can define for clean for the select then the multiplication sign
and then the next system type for here from and select from the employee. Okay, so now just
choose for the employee table. Okay, so just choose for the employee table and next system here
choose for this the order by and here I'll just type this is the salary and create for the
listening order. Okay, and the next system here we can use for the phase first. Okay,
if you TCH, okay, first or three rows, row only. So now perfectly type and just here create
for another new query and just open for here select then start and from here it is called the
employee table and then select also now just try select execute and you can see here
record perfectly for the employee table and now here is for add the case and now let's see the
here and it's just select table. Okay, so now choose for this and here this the employees. Okay,
so here are perfectly done and here is perfectly disabled for the particular this data query
and perfectly see the result. Okay, so here in this session is completely done and here are
perfectly used for the limit clause. Okay, so thank you for watching and bye.